Guide to the Rice University Photograph Files, 1910-2015 UA 363
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Campus View, Interiors and Groups of Buildings photographs
  - Campus aerial views (1991)
  - Campus aerial views (1992)
  - Campus aerial views (1998)
  - Campus aerial views (2000's)
  - [Proposals for] Campus additions
  - Campus area in front of Anderson Hall, with Fondren Library in background
  - Campus bookstore
  - Campus construction
  - Campus flooded
  - Campus general plan, 1909 and earlier proposals
  - Campus general plan, 1910
  - Campus general plan, 3/16/1910 proposal
  - Campus general plan, 7/1910 proposal
  - Campus map 1967
  - Campus n.d.
  - [General] Campus scenes (2 folders)
  - Campus scenes: copy photos and paintings
  - Campus site
  - [Plan of central] Campus with addition to Anderson Hall, 1980
  - Chapel, Rayzor
  - Chemical Engineering Dept.
  - Chemistry Building - exterior
  - Chemistry Building - exterior architectural details
  - Chemistry Building, parts of Abercrombie and Anderson Hall
  - Chemistry and Physics Buildings
  - Chemistry Lecture Hall
  - Classrooms/classes, general
  - Cohen House and Palmer Memorial Chapel
  - Cohen House fountain
  - Cohen House gardens
  - Commons
  - Community Garden
  - Construction
  - Courtyard - Rice Memorial Center (RMC)
  - Craig, Hardin - plaque
  - Electronic Music Studio
  - Ellinston Airfield
  - Entrance Gates
  - Entrance Gates - from Main Street
  - Facilities and Engineering Maintenance Shops
  - Faculty Chamber
  - Farish Gallery
  - Fondren Library and Cloisters connecting Anderson Hall
  - Football training room
  - Freehand Drawing Room
  - Galveston Harbor / Bay
  - [Keith Weiss] Geological Laboratories, M.D. Anderson Biological Lab - construction
  - [Keith Weiss] Geological Laboratories, M.D. Anderson Biological Lab - exterior
  - [Keith Weiss] Geological Laboratories, M.D. Anderson Biological Lab - interior construction
  - Geology and Biology Buildings, RMC
  - Hamman Hall and Wiess Geology Building
  - Hanszen College, Mechanical Lab, Lovett Hall
  - Hanszen College (West Hall), Baker Library, South Hall exterior
  - Harris Gully
  - Houston
  - Houston Ship Channel
  - ICSA
  - Jitney Bus
  - Keck Hall
  - KTRU
  - Kyle Morrow Room (Fondren Library)
  - Laboratories, interior
  - Lamppost in front of Physics Building (top missing)
  - Library in Lovett Hall
  - Lovett Bench
  - Lovett Hall and Cohen House
  - Lovett Hall and Mechanical Lab (Power Plant)
  - Lovett Hall and Physics Building
  - Lovett Hall, from cloisters in front of physics building
  - Lovett Hall, Physics Lab and Lecture Amphitheater
  - Lovett Hall, Physics and Mech Lab
  - Lovett Hall snowscene
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab and Campanile exterior
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab Machine shop, Power house
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab, Physics Building and Lovett Hall
  - Media Center
  - Men's Dormitory Group, 1955
  - Navy ROTC plaque
  - Oshman Engineering Design Kitchen (OEDK) Dedication 2008
  - Owen Wister Dining Room
  - Owl on (Physics building?)
  - Physics and Chemistry buildings from Mech Lab
  - Physics Building and Lovett Hall
  - Physics Building, Lovett Hall, and Chemistry Building
  - Pitman Tower
    See also: Humanities Building
  - Princeton and Area
  - Print Making Studio
  - R Room
  - [Robert H.] Ray Courtyard
  - Rayzor Hall Language Lab
  - Religion, Department of
  - Residential Hall Commons, circa 1912
  - Residential Halls with Commons aerial views 1921 dummy envelopes
  - Rice Institute Site
  - Rice Playing Field
  - Rice, William Marsh - model for statue
  - Rice, William Marsh - statue
  - Richardson drinking fountain and sculpture
  - Road between Physics amphitheater and Bonner Lab
  - [The] Roost
  - Rose Gardens
  - Sammy's Cafeteria
  - Sarah Lane Lounge
  - "Scrims" by Robert Irwin
  - Sculpture by Geology and Biology Buildings
  - Sculpture in Engineering Quad
  - Sewall Courtyard
  - Sewall Gallery (Rice Art Gallery)
  - Shuttle bus
  - Sid Richardson College and Sewall Hall - construction 1970
  - [The] Sisters' Foundtain
  - South Plant
  - Space Science Lab
  - Stadium (new)
  - Stadium Surrounds, aerial view
  - Symonds Teaching Laboratory
  - Tennis Courts (new)
  - Trolley
  - Trophy Case
  - Tunnels
  - Valhalla
  - Van de Graaf generator
  - "Virgins' Walk"
  - Walkway to football stadium, circa 1930's
  - Weight training room
  - Weight training room renovation
  - Wiess and Hanszen Colleges
  - Will Rice and Bakers Colleges
  - Will Rice College, Mech Lab and Power Plant, Lovett Hall
  - Will Rice College Wall Damage
  - Willy's Pub
  - Woodson Research Center
- Series V: Rice related events photographs
  - 30th Anniversary lay-out for Houston Post anniversary edition
  - $33 million campaign
  - Allen Center Open House, Nov. 11, 1967
  - Alumni awards
  - Alumni Club President's Meeting, New York, Sept. 30, 1950
  - Alumni College
  - Alumni Day
  - Alumni Executive Board Lunch
  - Alumni Fun Run
  - Alumni Institute Lecture Series
  - Alumni Luncheon
  - Alumni meeting, Fall 1951
  - Alumni picnic
  - Alumni reception
  - Alumni Reunion 1919
  - Alumni trip to China, 1979
  - American Alumni, Council Conference, Jan. 1951
  - Anderson Aeronautic Colelction Transfer to WRC, 1986
  - Annual Fund Drives
  - Anthropological dig in iran, 1964-66
  - Anti-Vietnam demonstration, 1968/69
  - Archaeology expedition, 1982
  - Archi-Arts Ball, Feb. 3, 1922
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1924
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1925
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1926
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1927
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1931
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1932
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1933
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1938
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1941
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1947
  - Archi-Arts Ball, late 1950's
  - Archi-Arts Ball, 1960
  - Archi-Arts Ball, n.d.
  - Archi-Arts (photocopies from Campanile)
  - Art Exhibits
  - [Lynn] Ashby visit 1983
  - Astronaut press conference, Oct. 3, 1962
  - Auto-Gyro demo on campus
  - Autry House laying of cornerstone, June 5, 1921
  - Autry House rededication, 1976
  - Awards
  - Axson Collection transferred to WRC
  - Baccalaureate 1916
  - Baccalaureate, June 10, 1917
  - Baccalaureate, June 9, 1918
  - Baccalaureate, June 8, 1919
  - Baccalaureate, June 6, 1920
  - Baccalaureate, June 5, 1921
  - Baccalaureate, June 11, 1922
  - Baccalaureate 1923
  - Baccalaureate 1924
  - Baccalaureate 1925
  - Baccalaureate 1926
  - Baccalaureate 1927
  - Baccalaureate 1928
  - Baccalaureate 1929
  - Baccalaureate 1930
  - Baccalaureate 1931
  - Baccalaureate 1932
  - Baccalaureate 1933
  - Baccalaureate 1934
  - Baccalaureate, June 2, 1935
  - Baccalaureate 1936
  - Baccalaureate, June 6, 1937
  - Baccalaureate, June 5, 1938
  - Baccalaureate, June 4, 1939
  - Baccalaureate 1940
  - Baccalaureate 1941
  - Baccalaureate 1942
  - Baccalaureate, May 30, 1943
  - Baccalaureate, Feb. 27, 1944
  - Baccalaureate, Fall 1944
  - Baccalaureate, March 3, 1946
  - Baccalaureate 1967
  - [The] Bacchae
  - Baker 13
  - Baker College feasts
  - Baker College Shakespeare Festivals and productions
  - [James A. III] Baker donates papers to Rice Univ. 1985
  - Baker Institute Announcement
  - Baker Institute Conference
  - Baker Institute Groundbreaking Oct. 20, 1994
  - Balloon launches
  - Banquet at Rice Hotel, Nov. 21, 1963
  - Bartlett Gift
  - Baseball College World Series Championship 2003
  - Baudoin, King of Belgium visit
  - Beer Bike Races
  - Bioengineering Program 1969
  - Biology Retreat 1918
  - Bonfire
  - "Breakin' a Leg"
  - British Educational Mission Visit, Nov. 1918
  - Brochstein Pavilion sneak peek, April 25, 2008
  - Brown College Associates Night
  - Brown College party
  - Brown School of Engineering dedication, 1975
  - Buckyball events
  - [Wm. F.] Buckley lectures 1985, 1969
  - Burke, Admiral Arleigh A. visit, Feb. 16, 1957
  - "Butley" - Wiess drama
  - C.E.'s of 1950
  - Carnival 1977
  - Centennial Educational Conference dinner, Indianapolis, IN, May 5, 1920
  - Centennial 2012
  - Chamber of Commerce dinner, Rice Hotel, April 18, 1946
  - Chemistry Building groundbreaking, June 4, 1923
  - Cities Service Company's check presentation: Dec. 11, 1979
  - Class of 1918 reunion, c. 1943
  - Class of 1919 reunion, c. 1934
  - Class of 1927 reunion, c. 1977
  - Class of 1929 reunion, c. 1979
  - Class of 1936 reunion
  - Class of 1939 reunion
  - Class of 1941 reunion, 1991
  - Class of 1945 - 30th reunion, 1965
  - Class of 1952 homecoming dinner
  - Class of 1954 reunion
  - Class of 1956 - 50th reunion
  - Cohen House laying of cornerstone, July 26, 1927
  - "College Bowl," General Electric show on NBC, Rice team, 1966
  - College Bowl Luncheon 1966
  - College Bowl n.d.
  - College Night
  - Commencement 1916
  - Commencement, June 11, 1917
  - Commencement, June 10, 1918
  - Commencement, June 9, 1919
  - Commencement, June 7, 1920
  - Commencement, June 6, 1921
  - Commencement 1922
  - Commencement 1923
  - Commencement 1924
  - Commencement 1925
  - Commencement 1926
  - Commencement 1927
  - Commencement 1928
  - Commencement 1929
  - Commencement 1930
  - Commencement 1931
  - Commencement 1932
  - Commencement 1933
  - Commencement 1934
  - Commencement, June 3, 1935
  - Commencement 1936
  - Commencement, June 7, 1937
  - Commencement 1938
  - Commencement 1939
  - Commencement 1940
  - Commencement 1941
  - Commencement 1942
  - Commencement, March 31, 1943
  - Commencement 1944
  - Commencement, Fall 1944
  - Commencement, March 4, 1946
  - Commencement 1955
  - Commencement 1963
  - Commencement 1964
  - Commencement 1968
  - Commencement 1970
  - Commencement 1972
  - Commencement 1973
  - Commencement 1974
  - Commencement 1975
  - Commencement 1977
  - Commencement 1978
  - Commencement 1979
  - Commencement 1981
  - Commencement 1982
  - Commencement 1983
  - Commencement 1985
  - Commencement 1986
  - Commencement 1987
  - Commencement 1991
  - Commencement 1992
  - Commencement 1993
  - Commencement 1994
  - Commencement 1995
  - Commencement 1997
  - Commencement 1998: Prizes and Awards, Cohen House May 8
  - Commencement 1998: WWII Era Graduates in Academic Quad and Cohen House May 9
  - Commencement 1999
  - Commencement 2000
  - Commencement 2002
  - Commencement, unidentified
  - Concerts
  - Construction
  - Continuing Education, School of- renaming ceremony
  - Continuing Studies "Class Reunion" 1993
  - Convocation 1976
  - Corporate Associates Seminar, April 20, 1978
  - Corporate Associates Seminar, Nov. 21, 1978
  - Cotton Bowl 1950
  - Cotton Bowl 1954, 1957
  - Craig, Dr. Hardin Jr. reirement party, Sept. 20, 1968
  - Dances
  - Demonstrations
  - Design Fete 1967
  - Dow Chemical Plant visit, Freeport, TX, 1957
  - EBLS reception for new members, 1918
  - Economic Summit 1990
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. visit, Oct. 24, 1960
  - Elections
  - Energy Day
  - Engineering Alumni lunch, Oct. 1954
  - Engineering Show 1928, 1938, 1954
  - Engineering Show, n.d.
  - Ernst, Max exhibition
  - F.E. and P. (2 folders)
  - Faculty Club Open House
  - Faculty reception 1973
  - Faculty Women's Club 50th Anniversary party, Feb. 10 1971
  - Fine Arts Showcase 1972
  - Fire drill
  - [aftermath] Fire in Dean Wierum office
  - Firemen's Memorial Service
  - [Campus] Flood; 1997
  - [Campus] Floods
  - Fondren flood (1966)
  - Fondren Library automated charging system 1966
  - Fondren Library computer project
  - Fondren Library parties
  - Fondren Library rededication and dedication of Graduate Research Wing, April 19, 1969 (b&w)
  - Fondren Library rededication and dedication of Graduate Research Wing, April 19, 1969 (color)
  - Fondren Library 30th birthday party, Nov. 9, 1979
  - Fondren Saturday Night, April 2, 1980
  - Football
  - Founders Day Dinner, Rice Hotel, April 14, 1941
  - French Mission visit, Dec. 9, 1918
  - French Mission visit, April 2, 1937
  - Freshman orientation 1962
  - Freshmen picnic
  - Friends of Fondren Galas/events
  - Friends of the Fondren Library Society dedication of the Kyle Morrow Memorial Room in
  - FFLS meeting, Feb. 6, 1975
  - FFLS presentation of scroll to Dr. Killop
  - Fund council meetings
  - Gamma Ray balloon launch
  - Garden Party 1919
  - Garden Party, June 7, 1920
  - Garden Party 1921
  - Garden Party, June 12, 1922
  - Garden Party 1923
  - Garden Party 1924
  - Garden Party 1925
  - Garden Party 1926
  - Garden Party 1927
  - Garden Party 1928
  - Garden Party 1929
  - Garden Party, June 9, 1930
  - Garden Party 1931
  - Garden Party 1932
  - Garden Party 1933
  - Garden Party, June 3, 1935
  - Garden Party 1936
  - Garden Party, June 7, 1937
  - Garden Party, June 6, 1938
  - Garden Party 1940
  - Garden Party for President and Mrs. A. Lawrence Lowell
  - Geology Dept. expeditions
  - Gifts
  - Gilbert & Sullivan Society Productions
  - [Hackerman] Gold medal award - American Institute of Chemists, Anaheim, CA, March 11, 1978
  - [Texas] Governor's Debate 2002
  - [Wm.] Goyen Tribute 4-84
  - Graduate House dedication-opening, 1-84
  - Greased Pole Climb 1960's
  - Great Gatsby party 1984
  - "Grigsby B" movie filming
  - Groundbreaking for John L. Cox Mechanical Engineering Building
  - Guadalajara, Mexico Trip 1966
  - Hackerman, Gene Luncheon
  - Hackerman, Norman Dinners and Receptions
  - Hackerman, Norman inauguration album
  - Hall, Walter and Helen reception, Woodson Research Center
  - Hamman Hall concert
  - Hanszen College fire, 1975
  - Hartsook Dinner, May 9, 1970
  - Hazing, 1960
  - "Hello Hamlet"Hillel meeting, May, 1956
  - Herring Hall Dedication
  - Herring Hall Groundbreaking
  - Hillel Meeting, 1956
  - [Gen. & Mrs. Maurice] Hirsch book donation 1982
  - Hoffman, Abbie affair, 1970
  - Homecoming, Nov. 5, 1951
  - Homecoming, 1952
  - Homecoming 1953
  - Homecoming 1954
  - Homecoming 1956
  - Homecoming 1958
  - Homecoming 1959-60
  - Homecoming 1962
  - Homecoming, Nov. 10-12, 1967
  - Homecoming 1968
  - Homecoming 1969
  - Homecoming 1970
  - Homecoming 1972 (50th year celebration)
  - Homecoming 1974
  - Homecoming 1975
  - Homecoming 1976
  - Homecoming 1977
  - Homecoming 1979
  - Homecoming 1982
  - Homecoming 1984
  - Homecoming 1985
  - Homecoming 1985 (reunion)
  - Homecoming 1992
  - Homecoming 1993
  - Hoover, Herbert visit to campus, May 11, 1925
  - Houston, William V. navy cruise, August 17-21, 1953
  - Humanities Building groundbreaking, Dec. 15, 1998
  - Hurricane Alicia clean-up 1983
  - [Julian S.] Huxley Papers dedication 1984
  - IBM Business Show, Feb. 1950
  - Jake Hess Tennis Stadium, Groundbreaking and Dedication 1970
  - Jefferson Davis Papers award 1982
  - Johnson, President Lyndon - visit
  - Jones School
  - Jordan, Barbara - lecture 1977
  - Jubilee of Sir George Gabriel Stokes, 1899
  - Junior Prom
  - Kennedy, John F. visit to Rice campus and Houston, Sept. 12, 1962
  - Kesey, Ken bus visit to Houston, 1966
  - Kid Party
  - Kissinger, Henry Visit
  - Landre, Louis - visiting Semicentennial lecturer
  - Laying of the cornerstone, Lovett Hall [Administration Building], March 2, 1911
  - Lecture - Space Week 1982
  - Lecture - Women's studies 1985
  - Leebron, David Inauguration
  - Leonardo de Vinci exhibit, Spring 1968
  - Ley Student Center groundbreaking
  - Library dedication of the Frank M. Bralley Memorial Library, College of Industrial Arts State College for Women, Denton, TX 1927
  - "A Little Night Music"
  - Lovett Casino Party
  - Lovett College dedication
  - Lovett College Winter Festival
  - Lovett Hall name change (from administration building) Dec. 4, 1947
  - Lovett Lounge dedication
  - Lovett Statue dedication 2012
  - Lowell, Pres. and Mrs. A. Lawrence of Harvard University visit to Rice Institute
  - Majors Day
  - Martin Luther King Day 1974
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1991
  - Masterson Texana Collection dedication
  - Matriculation 1970
  - Matriculation 1972
  - Matriculation 1975
  - Matriculation 1985
  - Matriculation general
  - May Fete, May 10, 1921
  - May Fete 1923
  - May Fete 1925
  - May Fete 1933
  - May Fete 1938
  - May Fete 1939
  - May Fete, undated
  - May FITE
  - McNair Hall Groundbreaking
  - Mechanical Engineering building groundbreaking
  - Memorial Center Fire, 1970
  - Memorial Center groundbreaking, Nov. 9, 1957
  - Michener, James visit to Woodson Research Center
  - Millionth volume celebration of Rice Library, April 22, 1979
  - "Mixed Signals"
  - [water on] Moon discovery, Oct. 21, 1971
  - [Kyle] Morrow Memorial Room dedication, Sept. 9, 1973
  - Mudd Building dedication 1983
  - NASA transfer ceremony
  - National Vietnam Moratorium Day
  - [Jess] Neely memorial service April, 1983
  - NEH Keats-Wordsworth Seminar
  - New freshman reception 1972
  - Nobel Prize (Curl, Shalley) Announcement
  - NROTC award, May 17, 1948
  - NROTC commissioning ceremony, Feb. 28, 1945
  - NROTC commissioning ceremony, June 29, 1946
  - NROTC training cruise, Summer 1947
  - NROTC Unit review, May 1958
  - Oil Bowl Game c. 1947
  - [formal] Opening of Rice Institute, Oct. 12, 1912
  - Orange Bowl
  - Orientation week
  - O-Week
  - Owl Day 1984
  - Parades
  - Parents' Day
  - Pep parade 1921
  - Pep rally
  - Pershing Day, Feb. 5, 1920
  - Pershing Pecan Tree Dedication April 14, 2012
  - Phi Beta Kappa, March 2, 1929
  - Philanthropy House party, April 21, 1919
  - Philosophical Society of Texas dinner, Dallas, Sept. 5 1939
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S. inauguration
  - [unveiling of] Pitzer portrait, Cohen House
  - Plays, 1923, 1940s
  - Pre-game party
  - President's Executive Luncheon #2
  - President's Executive Luncheon, Sept. 9, 1975
  - President's Executive Luncheon, Feb. 24, 1976
  - President's Executive Luncheon, April 29, 1976
  - President's Executive Luncheon, Feb. 15, 1977
  - President's Executive Luncheon, May 5, 1977
  - President's Executive Luncheon, Nov. 22, 1977
  - President's Executive Luncheon, Feb. 21, 1979
  - President's Executive Luncheon, Nov. 13, 1979
  - President's Open House 12-7-2004
  - President's Search White Paper 2003
  - Prince Philip's Visit
  - "R" Association Events
  - Reckling Park Groundbreaking and Dedication
  - Reunion 1936 [?]
  - Review of Science and Arts 1950
  - Rice Day 1951
  - Rice Day 1955
  - Rice Day, April 27, 1957
  - Rice Day, April 21, 1959
  - Rice Dramatic Club presentations 1922
  - Rice Exposition 1954
  - Rice Institute for Policy Analysis dinners, roundtables, luncheons
  - Rice Nite 1929
  - Rice Publishing Program
  - Rice University Fund Council 1972
  - Rice U. Presents TV Channel 13, Dr. Floyd S. Lear, Dr. Donald C. Mackenzie discuss "Thucydides and current events" Jan. 1961
  - Rice, William Marsh statue, turning of -1988
  - Rice, William Marsh statute unveiling and dedication, June 8, 1930
  - [Sid] Richardson College dedication
  - Rincon Oil Field Interest Purchase by Rice Institute
  - Romano FF and Juliet Radio Play
  - Rondelet
  - ROTC Review and Awards Ceremony
  - ROTC trip to Fort Polk, 1967
  - ROTC visit to USS Lexington, 1965
  - [George S.] Rupp inauguration
  - Sammy stolen
  - Sarah Lane Literary Society Pre-med formal, Feb. 14, 1948
  - Sarah Lane Lounge rededication 1984
  - Schirra, Wally (astronaut) press conference, RMC, Oct. 7, 1962
  - Semicentennial celebration and Kenneth S. Pitzer inauguration, Oct. 10, 1962
  - Semicentennial celebration, Oct. 10-12, 1962
  - Semicentennial celebration and visiting speakers, Oct. 11/12, 1962
  - Semi-formal, c. 1960
  - Senior banquet 1920
  - Senior Follies
  - Service Awards
  - Sewall Hall dedication
  - Sewall Hall groundbreaking ceremony
  - Sewall Hall laying of cornerstone
  - Sharp lectureship inauguration
  - Shepherd School concerts
  - Ship Channel (Houston) boat ride for Rice people
  - Ship christening, S.S. Rice Victory, June 16, 1945
  - Shoe Race
  - Slime parade c. 1921
  - Snow on campus (1918, 1930s, 1972, 1994)
  - Society of Rice University Women, first meeting 1968
  - Southwell, Sir Richard (Trinity College Fellow) - visit to Baker College 1958
  - [Ron] Stone Channel 2 TV ad 1985
  - Stokes, Sir George Gabriel Jubilee 1899
  - Streaking
  - Student activities
  - Student art show
  - Student election parade
  - Student greased pole contest
  - Student protests - faculty integration and Nixon Indo-China policy
  - Summer School/Spanish Summer Institute, 1964-June 1968
  - Summer School 1967 (Biology trip to Padre Island)
  - Summer School Program, Jr. and Sr. High, 1971, 1983
  - Summer School 1972
  - [1990 Economic] Summit
  - Superbowl, Jan. 1974
  - Taft, William H. visit
  - Tau Beta Pi Assoc. 64th Nat'l Convention at Rice, Oct. 9-11, 1969
  - Tea-Trike Race 1966, n.d.
  - TGIF
  - Thanksgiving Day reunion service, Nov. 27, 1919
  - Theatrical, General
  - Thesis Defense
  - The Trust scenes shot on campus
  - Tsanoff Bust Presentation, 1966
  - TV show 1968 "Confessions of Nat Turner"
  - University Forum TV telecast - Hardin Craig
  - Urban and Minority Affairs 1967
  - Veterans Day
  - Vision '87
  - [J. Russell] Wait Collection presented to Rice University, Oct. 1967
  - Water balloon fight 1960
  - Wiess College Cake Party
  - Wiess Tabletop Theater
  - Wilson, Dr. H.A. receiving Rice's Medal of Honor
  - Women's Golf Classic 1999
  - Women's Walkathon 1992, 1997
  - Worker's Conference, Fall '78
- Series VI: Sports and athletics photographs
  - [student] Archery
  - Athletic awards
  - Badminton
  - Baseball general
  - Baseball players, unknown
  - Baseball team 1916, 1921-23, 1926, 1955
  - Baseball team 1970-71
  - Basketball game photos
  - Basketball intramurals
  - Basketball team 1917
  - Basketball team photos
  - Basketball - women's
  - Bicycling
  - Fencing
  - Football, alumni
  - Football, general (2 folders)
  - Football, team photos
  - Football, women's and intramural
  - Golf
  - Handball
  - Health and P.E.
  - Intramurals
  - Ping Pong
  - Rugby
  - Soccer
  - Swimming
  - Tennis, men's
  - Tennis, women's
  - Track and Field meets
  - Track and Field team, 1919-20
  - Track & Field, women's
  - Volleyball [girls]
  - Volleyball, intramural
  - Volleyball, men's 1977/78
- Series VII: Oversize Rice photographs (people, places, events, sports)
  - Individuals and Group Photographs (Oversize 1)
    - Axson, Dr. Stockton (2 folders) (Oversize 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Brown, George R. (3 poses) (Oversize 1, Folder 3)
    - Burrus, Sidney C., in a group, 1976 (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - Cullinan, Joseph S. (signed) (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - Doty, James R., 1972 (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Ernst, Max 1972 Exhibit "Insight the Sight," many featuring Dominique de Menil (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - Hanszen, Henry Clay (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
    - Kessler, Susan, 1972 (Oversize 1, Folder 9)
    - Kikuchi Dairoku, 1912 (Oversize 1, Folder 10)
    - Lovett, E. O. (photograph of portrait) (Oversize 1, Folder 11)
    - Lovett, Dr. Edgar Odell, as an older man (1958 and after, 3 poses) (Oversize 1, Folder 12)
    - Manroe, Barbara, M.D., 1972 (Oversize 1, Folder 13)
    - McKillop, D. Allen Dugald (Oversize 1, Folder 14)
    - Moore, Charlie (Oversize 1, Folder 14a)
    - Pitzer, Dr. Kenneth S. (Oversize 1, Folder 15)
    - Poincare, Henri, 1912 (Oversize 1, Folder 16)
    - Revis, Shirley (later Redwine) (Oversize 1, Folder 17)
    - Rice, William Marsh - as an old man (3) and at age 34 (Oversize 1, Folder 18)
    - Rice, William Marsh, Jr. (nephew of William Marsh Rice) circa 1940 (Oversize 1, Folder 19)
    - Smith, D., 1972 (Oversize 1, Folder 20)
    - Turner, Anna Lay (3 poses) (Oversize 1, Folder 21)
    - Rimlinger, Gaston (Oversize 1, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified man, 1922 (Oversize 1, Folder 23)
    - Billups, Ed, Chemistry (Oversize 1, Folder 24)
    - Hall, Josiah (Portrait Gift of Mrs. R. Neff) (Oversize 1, Folder 25)
    - Images of men whose likenesses are carved on Lovett Hall Capitals (2 folders) (Oversize 1, Folder 26-27)